从根本上讲 "家庭第一"提案将
Fundamentally, the Families First bill
帮助我们最脆弱的孩子们
will help our most vulnerable kids,
比如那个想要圣诞老人在圣诞节
like the little boy in Seattle who asked Santa
教他读书识字的西雅图小男孩
to teach him how to read for Christmas.
那他是怎么写的心愿?
How did he write the note?
或者阿拉巴马州松树山的那个小女孩
Or the little girl down in Pine Hill, Alabama.
她通过母乳感染了HIV
She's HIV positive via breast milk,
但仍然梦想成为芭蕾舞者
but who still dreams of becoming a ballerina.
跳芭蕾确实得瘦
Well, they do need to stay thin.
- 他们为什么不能呢? - 怎么? 真的要瘦呀
- And why shouldn't they? - What? They do.
我们想给所有孩子舞动人生的理由 你知道吗?
We want to give all kids a reason to dance, you know?
耶稣受难日(复活节前的星期五)
- 先生? - 嗯？
- Sir. - Yes?
- 那个艾滋女孩 - 怎么?
- The HIV girl. - Yes?
总统在CBS采访中提到的那个
The one that the president mentioned in the CBS interview.
- 怎么了? - 是这样 那个天涯论坛上的一些人
- Yes? - All right, well, some people on Reddit
把细节拼凑起来人肉了她 现在整个镇子都知道她是谁了
put the details together, now the whole town knows who she is.
卧槽!
Fuck!
我更喜欢只有远景(古老的搜索引擎)
I preferred the Internet when it was just AltaVista
和玩星球大战的小屁孩的互联网
and that little Star Wars kid.
- 我们确实把这女孩曝露了? - 是的
- Did we definitely out this girl? - Yeah.
- 妈的 - 本来只有她的医生和校长知道
- Shit. - Only her doctor and her principal knew.
现在家长们不让孩子们去学校
Now parents are keeping their kids home from school
因为他们不想 原话是"传染上艾滋病"
'cause they don't want them to, quote, "Catch AIDS."
看来这个镇子还没受过撑同志大游行的洗礼
Well, there's a town with no Gay Pride parade
连他妈的图书馆都没有
or a goddamn library.
这个信息从哪儿来?
Where did this data come from?
我们怎么搞到她的医疗记录的?
How did we get her medical records?
还有为什么我们没有事先征得她父母同意?
And why didn't we ask her parents' permission?
谢谢你 十万个为什么先生
Oh, thank you, Question Man.
你刚拯救了整个城市 是这样吗?
You just saved the entire city. Or did you?
这件事火热得像迈克尔·贝(爱爆炸的变形金刚导演)
This is catching fire like a gas station
- 电影里的加油站一样 - 是的
- in a Michael Bay movie. - Yeah.
- 我们的底线是什么? - 我们要告诉总统吗?
- What's our line here? - Do we tell the president?
- 不要 - 不要?
- No. - No?
不要 她会惊慌失措的
No, she's gonna panic.
我们要查清更多事实 好吗?
We got to find out more facts, all right?
- 笨蛋们 解散吧 - 好吧
- Bozos, disassemble. - All right.
我一直觉得这件衣服的
I always feel like the ruching
皱褶特别能突显您的身材
on this one really accentuates your figure.
好的 你说的对 就穿这件
Okay, you're right. Let's go with that.
好的 我让服务生为您挂起来
Okay, I'll have the valet lay this out for you.
- 不 你来吧 - 哦
- No, you can do it. - Oh.
- 重现过去的轻松时光 是吧 - 是啊
- Reminds me of an easier time, you know? - Right.
或是我还能控制住问题的时候
Or a time whose problems I've suppressed.
是啊
Right.
我最爱的开心果来了
Oh, there's my favorite slice of fun.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是什么?
What is this?
Catherine 你抽烟了?
Catherine, you are smoking?
抽的电子烟 这不是重点
I'm vaping. That's not the point.
每周都是这样
This has been happening every week.
我的私人生活不应该被侵犯
My private life should be off-limits.
我看到你还在和Jason约会?
I see that you are still seeing Jason.
他很上相 对于他的年纪来说
He photographs well for his age.
夫人 苹果种植者协会
Ma'am, the Apple Growers Association
想用您的名字命名一种新品苹果
would like to name a new brand of apple after you.
是好苹果吗?
Is it a good apple?
- 烘焙用苹果(一般比较酸) - 去他妈的
- It's a baking apple. - Fuck 'em.
Bill Ericsson想在您走之前
Oh, and Bill Ericsson wants
见您 关于Catherine的事
to see you before you leave about Catherine.
- 抽烟的照片 - 电子烟
- The smoking photograph. - Vaping.
其实吧 "邮报"有一张ps的照片
Actually, there is a Photoshopped image in the "Post"
展示如果您在位八年后
of what you and Catherine
您和Catherine可能会长什么样
might look like if you had eight years in power.
天呐 我看起来像爷爷
Oh, my God, I look like Grandpa.
什么?
What?
他们对我的鼻子干了什么?
What did they do to my nose?
- 妈 我的事呢? - 啥?
- Mom, what about me? - Huh?
是的 我知道 这太无礼了
Yeah, I know. This is so disrespectful.
Mike在哪儿? 他还在做新闻简报(非正式不允许录像的新闻会议)?
Where is Mike? Is he still doing his gaggle?
- 是的 他还在 夫人 - 好的
- Yes, he's gaggling, ma'am. - All right.
总统会对关于小Jennifer Graham
Will the president be commenting
的突发新闻发表意见么?
on this breaking story about little Jennifer Graham?
呃 是的
Uh, yes.
我们将很快对这件事发表声明
We will very soon have a statement on that.
白宫泄露了
The White House
这个女孩的私人信息
released the girl's private information.
这些保密信息来自什么地方?
Where did this confidential data come from?
我知道总统证实了她确实感染了艾滋
I know that the president confirmed that she does have HIV.
而... 这个女孩 那个 感染了艾滋
And... the girl, that is, has HIV.
但是这个信息的来源尚未确定
But the provenance of that data has yet to be determined.
- 夫人 Mike正在... - 是的 我知道 他在哄这些狗仔
- Ma'am, Mike is just... - Yeah, I know, he's fluffing the hacks.
- 夫人 现在不是好时机 - 大家好
- Ma'am, this isn't a good time. - Hi, everybody.
Mike是在和大家分享他的甜蜜私房话呢?
Is Mike sharing his donut holes with y'all?
Lyle 希望你能带
And, Lyle, I hope that you're gonna bring
你女儿来参加复活节滚蛋活动
your daughter to the Easter egg roll.
谢谢您还记得我有个女儿 夫人
Oh, thank you for remembering I have a daughter, ma'am.
当然 是的
Oh, of course, yeah.
- 而且还记得我的名字 - 是的
- And also my name. - Yes.
- Lyle - Lyle 这是我的荣幸
- It's Lyle. - It's Lyle and it's my pleasure.
说到女儿
Hey, you know, speaking of daughters,
我想提一下Catherine
I just wanted to mention Catherine.
我知道她是第一女儿
I know that she's the First Daughter,
但是如果你们能给她的私人生活
but I would be very grateful if you guys
一点空间的的话 我将非常感激
would just give her a little bit of space in her private life.
我是想说 你们懂 我是那个摇滚巨星
I mean, you know, I'm the rock star.
她又不是明星
She's not the rock star.
所以 谢谢 非常感谢 很高兴见到各位
So, thanks, I appreciate it. Great to see everybody.
礼貌地问一句 夫人 您觉得一个8岁的艾滋病女孩
With respect, ma'am, do you think those same privacies
也应该被给予同样的隐私权吗？
should be given to an eight-year-old girl with HIV?
呃 嗯...
Um, well...
艾滋病确实是可怕的负担
HIV is a terrible burden
不过我很开心能帮助被其感染的家庭
and I'm very happy to be helping families who are affected by it.
这个不能写入报道
That is off the record.
好 这次简要汇报结束了
Okay, this briefing is over.
很开心见到你们 复活节滚彩蛋时再见吧
Nice to see you guys. I'll see you at the Easter egg roll.
-我的...我的朋友 嗯 -Lyle
- My... my friend, yes. - Lyle.
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
艾滋病打哪来的？
Where did HIV come from?
我觉得是有人上了只猴搞出来的
I think some guy fucked a monkey.
老天爷啊！
Jesus Christ!
麦克 你为啥没提醒我？
Why didn't you warn me about that, Mike?
夫人 你刚进来我就试着提醒过你
Ma'am, I tried to right when you came in.
-不 你没有 -你说得对 我没有
- No, you didn't. - You're right, I didn't.
-我本该提醒你的 -说得对
- I should have. - That's right.
-您是对的 夫人 -嗯 对 你完全没提醒我
- You were right, ma'am. - Yeah, no, you didn't warn me at all.
又他妈的咋的了？
What the fuck is happening?
是一起数据泄漏
It's a data breach.
医保 社保记录被某个
Medical, Social Security records were hacked
为我们工作的人黑了
by someone working for us
并且把数据用进了家庭第一提案发布会材料里
and then put into the Families First press pack.
那可不只是数据泄漏 那是数据崩漏
That's not just a breach. That's a data rupture.
你们说的这些狗屁对老娘来说没有意义
All of these words are meaningless to me.
我们现在要这样做 有个简单粗暴的主意
Here's what we're gonna do. It's an outrageous idea.
找到对这一切负责的人 然后炒了他
Let's find the person who's responsible and let's fire them.
夫人 这个项目有很大的数据流动性
Ma'am, there's so much data fluidity on this project,
罪犯很难被确定
the culprit will be hard to pin down.
好吧 媒体不需要这个罪魁祸首
Well, the press doesn't need the culprit.
他们只需要一个替罪羊
The press needs a culprit.
你知道 有一大群小姑娘
You know, there are hordes of young women
挤满了白宫西厢的大厅
who roam the halls of the West Wing.
- 然后呢？- 其中15%的人被聘用的目的就是被炒
- Yes? - 15% of them were hired to be fired.
对 我们叫他们女敢死队员
Yeah. We call them the Expendabelles.
- 孩子们 一点都不好笑
- That's not funny, boys.
- 不好笑 - 好了 Dan 去献祭一个处女吧
- No. - Okay, Dan, go sacrifice a virgin.
你平常周六的活要周五干了
Just another Saturday night.
- 这不好笑 Amy - 什么？怎么不好笑？
- That's not funny, Amy. - What? Why not?
喂 Egan 是不是有人要因为这艾滋事件要被炒鱿鱼？
Hey, Egan, is somebody gonna get fired over this AIDSnami?
哦 是耶 而且我负责开炮哦
Oh, yeah. And I'm in charge
生杀大权在我手 叫声Dan哥放你走
Hey, of the canning, Jonah. l'm the Dan who can.
好吧 那个 我只是
Okay, well, I was only
通过你参与了家庭第一提案 所以...
involved in the Families First bill via you, so...
那你的小老二呢？他怎么回事？
What about your side dick here? You tell him stuff?
哦 天 是啊 他比我参与的多多了
Oh, God, yes. He was more involved than I was.
他吃奶得劲儿都使上了
He was up to his thighs in it.
我没觉得我这么做过 先生
I don't think I was, sir.
你个奸诈小人一直在底下捣鬼爽不爽？
How's the view from down there, you snake?
-这话太难听了 -哦 难听？我们要统一战线
- It's harsh. - Oh, harsh? We need to be a unified front.
呃 你俩现在在忙啥？
Uh, what are you guys doing right now?
我俩在准备今晚副总统出席时的伴奏音乐
We're working on the veep's walk-on music for tonight.
-警察乐队 -配上温和的雷鬼乐
- The Police. - Law and order mixed with very mild reggae.
平衡的恰到好处
It's like a comforting balance.
嘿 Jonah 你愿意
Hey, Jonah, how would you
今晚多干点活吗？
like to be a little more involved tonight?
检查一下气球 彩带 烟火？
Supervise the balloons, the streamers, the fireworks?
- 好吧 -嗯？
- All right. - Yeah?
你知道我对这些很有品位
You know I got an eye for that.
这就是为什么我是个好摄影师
That's why I'm such a good photographer.
-当然 好的 -我喜欢烟火
- Absolutely. Yeah. - And I love fireworks.
声音啊 光芒啊
The noise, the lights.
基本上就这些
Mostly those aspects.
好吧 听着 我一会把细节发给你
All right, look, I'm gonna text you about this later.
我现在得走了 这个替罪羊跑不了了
Right now I've gotta go. This goat's not gonna scape itself.
感觉我被迫害了
I feel persecuted.
我就在坐等被媒体扔进池子里
I'm just waiting for the press to throw me in a pond
看我能不能自己漂起来
to see if I'll float.
蜜月期(第一个月)结束了 是吧？
Honeymoon's over, isn't it?
不过蜜月也跟坨屎似得
It was kind of a shitty honeymoon, too.
就像和你爸爸一起度的蜜月一样
Just like my actual honeymoon with Daddy.
我知道了 妈妈
I know, Mom.
"洋葱"恶搞了"邮报"的那张照片
"The Onion" Did a parody of that photo in the "Post."
哦 是吗？我喜欢"洋葱报"
Oh, really? I like "The Onion."
你卸任的时候是什么样子的
What you'll look like when you're leaving office,
跟你现在一模一样
except you look exactly like you do now.
好吧
Okay.
他们认为你只能做几个月的总统
They think you'll only be president for a few months.
-笑话是这个意思 -不 我懂 真的
- That's the joke. - No, no, I get it, yeah.
很有意思 真是有意思的事儿
That's funny. That's funny stuff.
我女儿的人生被毁了
Man on TV: My girl's had her life ruined.
总统是怎么查到她的信息的？
How did the president find out about her information?
这事已经越闹越大了
This thing has gotten way too big.
像我妈的猫一样
It's like my mom's cat.
总统只不过想帮助孩子们
The president is just trying to help children.
我不明白为什么
I don't understand
每个人都只不断关注消极的一面 你知道不？
why everyone keeps focusing on the negative, you know?
Gary 也许是因为 我们真的毁了一个女孩的人生
Maybe because, Gary, we ruined a girl's life.
消极 消极 消极
Negative, negative, negative.
Mike 国际父母协会
Mike, the National Parents Group
在下周媒体会上
cut the cord on supporting
会撤回对家庭第一提案的支持
Families First at next week's press event.
好啦 现在父母们都恨我们
Great, now parents hate us.
哦 天 欢迎来到我的童年
Oh, God, welcome to my childhood.
其实还有 成年
And adulthood, actually.
我们必须赶紧把这事结了
We need to shut the story down.
我知道 谢谢你 Sue
I'm aware of that. Thank you, Sue.
好吧 那你为什么还不了结这事儿？
Well, why haven't you shut it down?
你如果看见着火了 你是看到就扑灭它
If you see a fire, do you look at the fire
还是自己坐在一边 还说着"我知道呀"?
and put it out or do you just say, "I'm aware of it"?
Sue没资格教我怎么做我的工作
Sue cannot tell me how to do my job.
可她就是教了
She just did.
噢 我赌五毛这桶
Oh, I bet this baby
可以绽放出绚丽的烟花 是不是呀?
could sure spill a lot of glitter, am I right?
给老子放下
Put it down.
这东西要是擦枪走火射到你脸上
That thing goes off in your face,
想要取出来你眼里三叶草样子的火星
the surgeon will be tweezering tiny shamrocks
要用一周的时间手术
out of your eye jelly for a week.
先生 你好 我是Jonah Ryan
Hello, sir. Jonah Ryan.
现在 我还不能说我们是代表谁来的
Now, I cannot tell you who we represent,
不过至少可以告诉你
but let's just go so far
我的上司是个手握重权的人
as to say that my boss is a powerful guy,
而他的上司 我就更不用强调她的权势了...
and his boss, I cannot stress her power...
我知道了 他是副总统Doyle
I get it. He's VP Doyle,
她是临时总统Meyer
she's temporary President Meyer.
你们以为就这些五彩纸屑和迪斯科球
You think confetti and a disco ball's
就可以把这些政界的跳梁小丑都留在白宫?
gonna keep those clowns in the White House?
这 先生 如果你还想要做这笔生意的话...
Well, sir, if you would like us to take our business elsewhere...
-成熟点 行么? -我做过生意的人多了
- Grow up, huh?  - I do anyone.
我76年的时候就给杰里·福特吹过气球(40届总统)
I did balloons for Jerry Ford in '76.
像他那样的人 混球
Met him. Asshole.
那么你能给我们弄一个什么样的装扮套装?
So what can you organize for us?
-有一个总统套装 -哦 听起来很完美
- There's the Presidential. - Oh, that sounds perfect.
其实是最低级的 你们不会想要那个的
That's bottom of the range. You don't want that.
我命名成总统套装只是因为福特那个混蛋
I just named it Presidential because of that asshole Ford.
上面交代我们此次要大手笔来操办
We've been told to really go to town.
好 那你们需要来一个星光灿烂的炮仗
Well, then you want the Star-Spangled Banger.
或者是 红的 白的 还有各种欢呼
Or Red, White, and Whoo-hoo.
那 我们有什么有创意的法子来放音乐吗?
Now, will we have some sort of creative control over the music?
我才不管你那屌事 小子 反正我能拿到钱
I don't give a shit, son. I still get paid.
让我给你们秀秀我的好货
Let me show you what we got.
马里兰州陶森市Meyer竞选集会
-她在这儿 -嗨
- There she is. - Hey.
-嗨 我很激动 -嗯 很好
- Hey, I'm excited. - Okay. Good.
我会先为你热场子
I'll warm them up for you.
问题是 你希望观众有多热情?
Question is, how hot do you want them?
-热情似火 -你会讲那个蜗牛的笑话 对吧?
- Red hot. - Gonna do the snail joke, right?
这是你的标志性笑话 你的专利笑话
That's your trademark joke. Signature joke.
呃 你不必讲你的蜗牛笑话
Yeah, you don't have to do the snail joke.
太有趣了
It's so funny.
呃 Andrew 听着 我要问你一些问题
Uh, Andrew, listen. Let me ask you something.
你觉得这个艾滋病女孩事件会葬送我们的前程还是怎么地?
Do you think this HIV girl thing is killing us or what?
不 不 不 你会顺利度过的
No, no, no. You're gonna be fine.
你看 如今消息传播如此迅速 比如说我们有一部新的iPhone
Look, the news moves so quickly, we'll have a new iPhone
或者中国人会去芝加哥啥的
or the Chinese will be in Chicago.
-Amy 我能和你聊几句吗? -好的
- Amy, can I talk to you a sec? - Sure.
Doyle要用"你的每一次呼吸"作为他的入场曲
Doyle's using "Every Breath You Take" For his walk-on music.
他超爱那首歌 他都用了两次了
He loves that song. He got married to it both times.
每句话结尾都是"我盯着你呢(歌词)"
Every line ends with "I'll be watching you."
斯汀(警察乐队主唱)还不如用伪牙买加人口音
Sting might as well be singing
唱"我会拿得你的医疗记录"
"I'll access your medical data" In a fake Jamaican accent.
你玩儿得开心吗?
You having fun?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
-但工作也很努力的 -嗯哼
- But also working hard. - Mm-hmm.
- 谢谢关心 - 这是Chloe吗?
- Thank you for asking. - It's Chloe?
- 她是Ellie  -Lee
- It's Ellie. - Lee.
- Lee - Lee?
- Lee. - Lee?
-Lee - 啊
- Lee. - Ah.
你不可以换歌
You can't change the music.
它和灯光秀是组合配套的
It's all cued up with the light show.
去你妈的灯光秀 Jonah 有没有搞错?
Fuck the light show, Jonah, okay?
他可是副总统 不是新款雷克萨斯
He's the vice president, not the new Lexus.
-去他妈的灯光秀? -是的 去他妈的
- Fuck the light show? - Yeah, fuck it.
小心点烫 Ryan先生
Be careful, Mr. Ryan. It burns
就算你拿着这个隔热套还是烫手
your hand even through the corrugated sleeve.
-你非得这样吗? -除非有一个不会破坏Doyle
- Can you do this? - Is there a way to change
的灯光效果的音乐 否则免谈好呗?
Doyle's music without screwing up the lights?
-哦 当然 -太好了
- Oh, absolutely. - Great.
呃 我不确定 但是希望还是要有的
Well, I'm not sure, but positivity is the first step.
-说得好 -换成什么?
- Love it. - Change it to what?
-这不重要 -我真心没主意
- Doesn't matter. - I honestly have no idea.
你手机里有什么?
What do you have on your phone?
呃 大多数都是励志有声书
Well, it's mostly self-help audio books
和一些舒缓的录音带 我是个容易焦躁的人
and relaxation tapes. I'm quite an anxious man.
哦 你知道吗? 我还有些电影主题曲
Oh, you know what? I've got movie themes.
我们试试"虎之眼"(中的主题曲)
I'll cue "Eye of the Tiger."
好的 伙计们"虎之眼"可以吗?
Okay, guys, guys. "Eye of the Tiger"?
里面存在有争议的歌词吗?
Any controversial lyrics in that?
-没有 没有 -就这个 就放这首歌
- It's good. It's good. - Do it. Do it.
女士们先生们 有请美利坚合众国副总统
Ladies and gentlemen, the Vice President of the United States.
什么鬼?(Every Breath You Take-警察乐队)
What the fuck?
哦 哦 什么玩意儿?
Uh-oh. What?
我不知道这是什么情况
I don't know what's happened.
你知道 我通常用的是苹果的系统
You know, I usually use a Mac,
所以非要怪的话 这是Win8的错
so this is Windows 8's fault if anybody's.
众所周知 伟大的马克 吐温
You know, the great Mark Twain,
是我梦想能在现实中邀请来
one of my dream dinner party guests
- 共进晚餐的人之一
- in actual fact... -
曾说过...
once said that...
操他大爷的警察乐队
Screwed over by the Police.
我就是他妈的罗德尼·金(91年 黑人司机被警察殴打致死)
I'm Rodney fucking King.
又一个毁掉我竞选的大错铸成了
Another blunder to undermine my campaign.
这不是大错 只是一个不幸的失误
It's not a blunder. It was an unfortunate mistake.
嗯 按照大错误的定义来说 这个...
Yes, the definition of a blunder, so...
-好吧 -没有人会听歌词的啦
- Right. - Nobody listens to the words anyways.
是不啦? 我就闻歌起舞
You know? I just dance.
推特上有了 她做的每一件小事都是悲剧
Twitter has it. EVeryLittleThingSheDoeslsTragic.
那么话不多说 让我们有请...
So without further delay, please welcome onto this stage...
搞掂他们
Go get 'em.
美立坚合众国总统
The President of the United States.
他们爱死您了 女士 您简直像一个摇滚巨星
They loved it, ma'am. You were like a rock star.
不是斯汀 是科特·柯本(爆头自杀)那种 好吧 也不是他那种
Not Sting. Kurt Cobain. Well, not him.
这是我的集会 好吗 显然那些都是我的支持者
It was my rally, okay? My supporters, of course.
这就像收到你妈送给你的情人节礼物一样 懂吗?
It's like getting a valentine from your own mom, you know?
女士 我们的微型捐赠者们在减少
Ma'am, we're losing micro-donors.
我们将会只剩下纳米级捐赠者
We'll be down to nano-donors.
你什么意思 我们的微型捐赠者们在减少?
What do you mean, we're losing micro-donors?
-我们不能失去他们 他们是竞选的中坚力量 -是的
- We can't. That's our backbone. - Yes.
他们希望自己能从我们的数据库中移除掉
They want to be removed from our database.
他们不希望我们拥有他们的私人数据
They don't want us having their personal data.
总统女士 总统女士
Madam President! Madam President!
您什么时候会就Jennifer Graham的事发表声明?
When are you gonna make a statement about Jennifer Graham?
让这些小人物们意识到我们尊重他们是至关重要的
It's vital that these small-time nobodies realize we respect them, okay?
Jennifer Graham的姑妈说只有不称职的母亲
Jennifer Graham's aunt says only an unfit mother
才会对发生在她侄女身上的事毫不在乎
would be immune to her niece's suffering.
好吧 我得回应这个问题
Okay, I'm gonna have to answer that, all right?
我要在镜头前发表个声明
I'm gonna make a statement on camera.
您觉得这样做好吗 夫人?
Do you think that's the best move, ma'am?
我刚刚说过我应该做的事
The thing I just said that I should do?
我认不认为那是我应该做的事?
Do I think it's the thing I should do?
这是你该问的问题吗 Mike?
Is that your question, Mike?
我们决定做一个简短的声明
We've decided to make a quick statement.
呃 我只想简单地说
Um, I just want to simply say
我对于此次的数据泄漏并不知情
that I had no knowledge of this data breach.
但是作为总统 我将承担全部责任
But as president, I take full responsibility
因为这是我工作的一部分
because that's part of the job.
我会查出这次事件的罪魁祸首
I'm going to find out who's responsible
以及事件的原因及过程
and why it happened and how it happened.
最后 我想对Jennifer Graham和她的整个家庭表达我的歉……
And lastly, I want to extend my apologies to Jennifer Graham and her entire fam...
如果那样的话 对我们会是巨大的损失和极大的问题
If that happened, it would be hugely damaging and enormously problematic.
- 您好 总统女士 - 你好
- Hi, Madam President. - Hi.
夫人 找到了个替罪羊
Ma'am, got us a scapegoat.
那个在写作室写联席会议讲稿的女孩
Girl in the writers' room for the joint sessions speech.
她也在今晚的集会上 叫神幻Sally什么的
She was also at the rally tonight. Sci-fi Sally something.
-Ellie? -Chloe
- Ellie? - Chloe.
-Marie -Claire
- Marie. - Claire.
-是Lee -Gary说对了
- It's Lee. - Gary is right,
她的名字是Lee 她是个不错的员工
her name is Lee and she is a fine staffer.
擅长精读文件和政策分析
Great on close reading and policy analysis.
我从她身上看到了我自己的影子
I see splashes of myself in her.
我现在后悔我刚才的措辞
I now regret that phrase.
女士 美国家庭联协会撤销对您的支持
Ma'am, the American Family Group is pulling their support.
- 什么? - 是的
- What? - Yeah.
你从哪得到的消息?
Where did you get that from?
-一个匿名线报 -操
- An anonymous source. - Shit.
是我的嫂子 她在美国家庭协会工作
Who's my sister-in-law who works for the American Family Group.
-好吧 Dan -在
- Okay, Dan. - Yeah.
去把Lee炒了
Go fire Lee.
Mike 去宣布有人被解雇了
Mike, announce a head is rolling.
Ben和Amy 去把烟花的破事解决了
Okay, Ben, Amy, go fix this fireworks shit.
-Gary 去给我拿根能量棒 -好的
- Gary, I need an energy bar. - Yeah.
-不 我要苹果 -嗯
- No, apple. - Hmm.
-不 去他妈的 拿奶酪来 -哦
- No, fuck it, cheese. - Oh.
-呃 夫人…… -听着 Kent 我很抱歉 不过Chloe必须得走人
- Uh, ma'am... - Look, Kent, I'm sorry, but Chloe's got to go.
-不是Chloe 是Lee -好吧
- It's not Chloe, it's Lee. - Okay.
-不过 我不是要说Lee的事 是关于Catherine的事 -什么?
- And anyway, it's not Lee, it's Catherine. - What?
她想和一个反欺凌慈善组织合作
She wants to work with an anti-bullying charity.
什么? 她脑子进水了吗?
What, is she nuts?
我是说 这会
I mean, it's gonna make
让人觉得她的妈妈在欺凌她
it look like she thinks her mom bullied her.
好吧 我觉得
Well, I think she's
她可能认为这样会让人们更喜爱她
calculating that this will make her more likable.
对我他妈的反正没用
Not with me, it fucking won't.
女士 奶酪快到了
Ma'am, cheese is on its way.
先给您一个香蕉过渡一下
Here's an interim banana.
皮都剥不开
It doesn't even work.
-所以我明天就要走吗? -你现在就得走
- So do I leave tomorrow? - You leave now.
除非你是来观光的
Unless you're on a tour,
否则你明天不会出现在白宫
you will not be at the White House tomorrow.
如果我哭会有用吗?
What if I cried?
像电影里的女人那样惨哭?
Like the women do in movies?
没用的 你面前的这个人
Wouldn't work. You're talking to a guy
曾经在沙县小吃解除婚约 然后还点了甜点
who once broke off an engagement at an Applebee's, then ordered dessert.
能把你的通行证给我吗?
May I have your pass?
和你在一起工作很开心…… Lee
It was a pleasure working with you... Lee.
随着更多的
With more
医疗信息泄漏丑闻的真相浮出水面
revelations in the Medileaks scandal emerging,
谁知道呢?
who knew?
有没有人在掩盖实情
Was there a cover-up?
如果是的话 这条指挥链的终端究竟握在谁手上?
And if so, how far up the chain of command did it go?
呃 正顺着我身上的这条指挥链往上爬呢
Ugh, it's working its way up my chain of command.
我觉得已经到我的胰腺了
I think it's reached my pancreas.
白宫公布出来的私人医疗信息
Private medical details released by the White House
又暴露了五个孩子的身份……
have now identified five more children...
还真符合复活节这个日子 这个新闻就特么死不了
Fittin that for Easter this story refuses to fucking die.
就没有别的新闻了吗?
Is there no other news?
埃博拉疫情怎么样了? 我可喜欢埃博拉了
Whatever happened to Ebola? I loved Ebola.
我们把某人扔出了救生艇
So we threw someone off the life raft.
就没人想着告诉鲨鱼一声吗?
Did no one think to tell the sharks?
女士 我觉得那个女孩的职位不够高
Ma'am, I don't think the girl was senior enough.
我们得找一个更大的替罪羊
We need to cut the throat of a bigger goat.
那么下一个被送上断头台的是谁呢?
So who's next for the guillotine?
- 呃 Jonah Ryan - Jonah?
- Uh, Jonah Ryan. - Jonah?
是的 夫人 我一直在为着这样的机会把他养肥
Yes, ma'am. I've been fattening him up for just this occasion.
- 呃 Jonah Ryan - Jonah?
- Uh, Jonah Ryan. - Jonah?
是的 夫人 我一直在为着这样的机会把他养肥
Yes, ma'am. I've been fattening him up for just this occasion.
-什么? -我给他配了一个助手
- What? - I got him a staff.
而且我让他参与了家庭第一提案
And I got him involved in Families First.
我甚至让他参与了竞选活动
I even got him on the campaign.
负责昨晚烟火和音乐的就是他
He's the one who did the fireworks and the music for last night.
是他啊? 让他丫的滚犊子
That was him? Off with his fat head.
他很有可能与整个数据泄漏事件有关
I can easily link him to the whole data breach thing.
-好像他啥都不知道似的. -不好意思
- It's like he has no sense of what's going on. - Excuse me.
你没看到Dan还在说话嘛?
Did you know that Dan was in the middle of speaking?
-是的是的 -谢谢
- Yeah, yeah. - Thank you.
更何况他天生长着这样一张罪犯脸
And plus he's got that whole inherently guilty look.
你知道的 就是那种打飞机时受惊的脸
You know, that kind of surprised masturbator face.
-这样… -是啊 他确实是这样
- The... - Yeah, he does.
行动吧 让他走人 把他扔到黑锅下面去
Do it. Get rid of him. Throw him under a bus.
如果这个锅能够大的话
If you can find one that's long enough.
嘿 Egan 副总统想见总统
Hey, Egan, VP wants to see the P.
他认为应该找个官帽更大的人做替罪羊
He thinks a bigger head needs to roll, okay?
要那种官帽大得像复活岛一样的家伙
Like a massive Easter Island-sized head.
-嗯 -不 不
- Hmm. - No. No.
你瞧瞧我 我这顶官帽可小啦
Look at me, I've got a small head.
只有童帽那么大
I could wear a child's hat.
另外…
Besides...
我知道你就是那个散播Danny Chung谣言的人
I know about you spreading the Danny Chung torture rumor.
那个 已经是个没有用的筹码了 Jonah
Well, that's useless leverage right now, Jonah,
因为你已经被认定是那个
because you have all the credibility of someone
盗取了一个生病孩子的医疗记录的人
who hacked the medical records of a sick child.
-不是的… -嘿 "长脸树精"
- No... - Hey, "I Am Groot,"
别再和这个"漂亮女人"交换唾液了
stop swapping spit here with "Pretty Woman"
给我把Brock和Hunter找来
and get me Brock and Hunter.
没问题 对不起 我正打算去呢
Absolutely. Sorry, I was just on my way to go do that.
那是个重要的会议 知道吗? 是很重大的(精液的)
It's an important meeting, okay? It's seminal.
哦 嘿
Oh, hey.
这个搞笑的笑话你之前已经说过啦
You already did this great joke.
尼玛 老兄 这家伙的蛋蛋真大
Damn, man, this guy's balls are so big,
简直就是俩奶子 是吧? 奶蛋Johnny
they're practically tits. Huh? Johnny Tit-balls.
是啊 别老挤这乳器了
Yeah, don't squeeze the milkers too much.
乳器 说的好
Milkers. Love it.
你要解雇我?
You were firing me?
刚刚这是什么情况?
What the hell was that?
没什么 只是说说笑话
Nothing. It's just jock stuff.
你知道 就是男士们会开的玩笑
You know, just guys having fun.
那可不是啊 Jonah 那是性骚扰
That isn't, Jonah. That's sexual harassment.
老天 他经常这样对你嘛?
Jesus, does he do that to you all the time?
没啦 不算是经常吧
No, not all the time.
有时候 但不总是这样
Sometimes, but not all the time.
这就是兴致来了
It's just high spirits.
Ryan先生 他们没有金枪鱼三明治了
Mr. Ryan, so they were out of tuna melts,
所以我即兴为你准备了这个龙虾咖喱卷
so I improvised and I got you this lobster curry roll.
好了 闭嘴 Jeeves
All right, look, zip it, Jeeves.
我正在开除你的老大呢
I'm in the middle of firing your boss.
不是吧 因为那个竞选数据的事儿?
Wow, over the campaign data thing?
-什么事? -那个关怀小广告
- The what? - The I Care mailer.
好吧 不是嘛?
All right, no?
从你的表情来看 我觉得你还不知情
I'm picking up from your facial cues that you don't know.
我给你四个字的面部表情… "煞笔快说"
Here's four verbal cues for you... "Tell me now, asshole."
好吧 那个广告
Well, that mailer was
是故意发给那些近期失去子女的夫妇的
deliberately directed at recently bereaved parents.
失去子女的夫妇?
Bereaved parents?
是啊 在竞选团队里有人用了那次找到艾滋女孩的数据泄漏
Yeah, someone from the campaign used the child mortality data
来得到死亡儿童的数据
from the same data breach that identified the HIV girl.
好了 你们俩笨熊听好了
Okay, Yogi and Boo-Boo,
不要和任何人提起这件事 懂么?
you say nothing to anybody. You understand me?
- 好的 - 但是 明显你们没懂
- Yes. - Well, obviously you don't,
因为刚刚你们俩还特么的在说呢
'cause you just fucking spoke.
- 哦 - 日了狗了!
- Oh. - Shit!
Amy 通往地狱的大门已经打开了 咱俩要结个伴了
Amy, the gates of hell have opened and you are my plus one.
你不能跟欺凌行为扯上关系
You cannot be associated with bullying
否则人们会认为你是受我欺凌的
because people are going to think that you were bullied by me.
我不是受你欺凌 我是因为你而受欺凌
I wasn't bullied by you, I was bullied because of you.
需要我回避一下嘛?
Did you want me to leave?
-不 不用 -要的
- No, no. - Yes.
不 你没有受欺负啊 甜心
No, you weren't, sweetheart.
是的 我有 而且很痛苦
Yes, I was and it was miserable.
那好吧 我为我个人的成功表示抱歉 Catherine
Well, I apologize for my success, Catherine.
直到现在我才知道
I had no idea until this very moment
你在成长的道路上受虐待 不幸福 还很痛苦
that you had a tortured, unhappy, miserable upbringing.
但是你还是不能提欺凌这个词 亲爱的
You're gonna have to drop the bullying thing, though, honey.
不 我不会这么做的
No, I'm not gonna drop it.
你还想不想在感恩节去夏威夷了?
Do you want to go to Hawaii at Thanksgiving?
你还对你奶奶留下的蓝宝石耳环感兴趣嘛?
Are you interested in Memaw's sapphire earrings?
你正在用欺凌我的方式让我不要去参与到反欺凌的活动里去?
Are you bullying me into dropping an anti-bullying charity?
我有嘛 Gary?
Gary, am I?
你是在教育孩子
You're parenting.
是啊 我也这样想
Yeah, well, too, I might add.
- 等等等等 同志们 - 我们一会再解释
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, guys. - We'll explain later.
不 我们绝对不会解释的
No, we won't. We'll never explain.
夫人 Catherine得回避一下
Ma'am, Catherine needs to leave.
好的 Catherine 起来 出去
Okay, Catherine, up, out.
我勒个去啊
For fuck's sake.
好了 别再说脏话了
All right, that's enough with the F words.
谢谢了 我对她的行为表示抱歉…
Thank you very much. I apologize for her behav...
怎么了?
What is it?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
那好吧 会议结束了那就 谢啦
Well, great meeting, then, thanks.
夫人 如果我们告诉你 你就会知道了
Ma'am, if we tell you, you'll know,
如果你知道了 就得受牵连
and if you know, you'll be implicated.
那么 你们为什么不告诉我事情经过
Well, then, why don't you tell me
然后让我来决定我是否知道了呢?
and I'll decide whether or not I know it?
夫人 上个月的竞选邮寄广告里
Ma'am, a direct mail campaign went out last month
图片上出现了你和孩子们
with pictures of you with babies and children.
对 这很成功
Yeah, it was a huge success.
女士 它的目标群体是最近失去了子女的夫妇
Ma'am, it targeted recently bereaved parents
并用了盗取的政府数据
using stolen government data.
这样...
Well...
那可是重罪了
that's a federal crime.
-对 -没错 是重罪
- Yes. - Yes, it is.
你们可能要进监狱
You could go to jail.
是 女士 我们要坐牢了
Yes, ma'am, we could go to jail.
对 你们要坐牢了
Yeah, you could go to jail.
哇
Wow.
我们玩完了? 是不是这样?
We're fucked? Is that what this is?
"恐怕这已经扩散到肝部没救了"的玩完了?
"I'm afraid it's spread to the liver" Fucked?
女士 我们认为是在卫生福利部的一个学生志愿者
Ma'am, we think it was a student
和朋友一起干的 但他现在已经不在那儿了
volunteer with a pal at HHS, but he's gone now.
如果我们打起精神 以守为攻拼死一搏
If we can just hold our nerve and maintain a bunker mentality...
别和我提那操蛋的以守为攻
Don't give me that bunker shit.
希特勒进了地下室防守
Hitler went into a bunker.
出来之后就不是元首了 不是吗?
When he came out, he wasn't chancellor anymore, was he?
而且他还挂了
Plus he was dead.
我告诉你 就算希特勒现在还活着
I'll tell you something, if he were alive right now,
他现在也巴不得想离我远点
he'd be very anxious to distance himself from me at this moment.
这个秘密只能留在这间四...
We need to keep this within these four...
这个椭圆办公室里
Or this one curved wall.
我们要阻止媒体
We need to stop the press
不能让他们再继续挖料了
dead so they don't dig into this any further.
这就意味着要职人员请辞谢罪
And that means a major resignation.
得有个人 如果你们要后进先出的话 那我就得滚蛋了
A face. Although, if you operate last in, first out, I'm screwed.
女士 我有个提议 需要和你谈谈
Ma'am, I have a proposal I need to speak with you about.
好吧 Amy Ben 你俩留下
Okay, fine. Amy, Ben, you stay.
其他人都出去
Everybody else, just get out.
我来做交辞呈的人吧
I need to be the one to go.
你? 不 不
You? No, no.
是的 总统女士
Yes, Madam President.
这种迎头痛击 我是你最大的安全气囊
This is a head-on collision and I'm your biggest air bag.
好 所以我们需要发表一篇
Okay, so we need to issue
关于那个艾滋病女孩的积极(阳性)声明
a positive statement about the HIV girl.
不是阳性 措辞不当
Not positive. Wrong word.
Mike 刚刚谈到我可能被炒鱿鱼时
Mike, did I see you smiling
你是在偷笑吗?
when it was suggested I might be fired?
我? 没有啊 我才没笑呢
Me? No. I... I wasn't smiling.
我只是抿嘴而已 因为嘴唇有点儿干
I was stretching my lips because I have very dry lips,
我的医生叫我多抿嘴唇
and my doctor said, "You should probably stretch them."
所以我只是听从医生建议而已 像...
So I was following medical advice. Like...
-像这样 -这就是那你的解释?
- Like that. - That's what you're going with?
哇 听着 如果你玩扑克的话 一定叫上我
Wow. Listen, you ever play poker, I want in,
因为你根本就不会撒谎
'cause you are one terrible liar.
你太可悲了 因为撒谎就是你的工作
And that's sad 'cause that's your whole job.
你为啥用我旁边的便池？
Why are you using the urinal next to me?
-你应该留个间隔 -我已经开始尿啦
- You leave a gap. - I've already started.
用那个小的会有尿溅到我
The little one gives me splash-back.
但是你也得留个空位 毕竟我们不是尿友
Still, you leave a gap. We're not piss buddies.
该死 你还可以控制你的前列腺嘛
Damn, that's some kind of prostate control.
好好珍惜吧 朋友
Treasure it, my friend.
所以 你是想知道
So, you want to know if the
总统有没有告诉我她要解雇谁 对吧?
president told me who she's firing, right?
-是 -是我
- Yeah. - It's me.
在她宣布前你不能告诉任何人
You don't tell anyone until she's made an announcement.
-明白 -一个字也不会泄漏
- You got it? - Yeah, not a word.
用你手上握着的宝贝起誓?
You swear by everything you hold dear in your hand right now?
我发誓
I do.
我以我宝贝Dan的名义发誓
I swear on King Danny.
这是复活节滚蛋活动 我发现只有篮子没有蛋
This is an Easter egg roll and I just see baskets with no eggs.
Gary 坐在第一排讲故事的孩子
Gary, front row for the story reading
必须是那些有着最顽强膀胱的(最能憋尿)
needs to be the children with the strongest bladders.
-我没听懂  啥意思啊-各位
- I don't even know what that means. - Guys.
-感谢上帝 -为什么让我拿彩蛋?
- Oh, thank God. - Why am I carrying eggs, huh?
-我现在要忙艾滋病的事 -不 别交给我
- I'm up to my eyeballs in HIV. - No, no, don't give them to me.
那里有只6英尺高的兔子
There's a six-foot bunny
拿着30只勺子 你肯定能找到他
out there with 30 spoons. You can't miss him.
-是Ben被炒鱿鱼 -不可能
- It's Ben. - No way.
不 Mike 你说谁被炒?
No, who's getting fired, Mike.
-什么? -没错
- What? - Yeah.
我找到另一只彩蛋了
I found another one.
Greg 很感谢你的服务
Well, thank you for your service, Greg.
很高兴我的一位海军能穿成只兔子
Very happy to have one of my Marines in costume.
-你客气了 总统 -事实上 我很高兴你在这
- You're welcome, ma'am. - Actually, I'm really glad you're here.
这些孩子吓到我了
These kids terrify me.
但我相信你还经历过更糟糕的情况
But I guess you've seen worse.
你曾两次出征阿富汗?
You did two tours of Afghanistan?
是的 总统 我最好的朋友在那牺牲了
Yes, ma'am. I saw my best buddy die over there.
他被简易爆炸装置炸成碎片
Blown to pieces by an IED.
Egan先生 你现在有空吗?
Mr. Egan. You have a moment?
-当然 -好 我等下回给你
- Sure. - Yeah, I'll call you back.
-嘿 Dan -我以为你辞职了呢
- Hey, Dan. - I thought you resigned.
我想总统改变主意了
I guess the president changed her mind.
世事无常 我的朋友
It's a fickle world, my friend,
你就遭遇变故了
and you've just been fickled.
不 不 这不是真的
No. No, this is not... This is not real.
没错 Dan 你只是在做梦
You're right, Dan. It's a dream.
接着我和Kent就会变成
And me and Kent are about to turn into
两个妖娆的拉拉队长和你打炮
two horny cheerleaders and start making out.
所以说我被炒了? Ben 请别跟我说我被炒了
So am I fired? Please, Ben, don't say that I'm fired.
-你没被炒 -太特么感谢你了
- You're not fired. - Oh, thank fuck for that.
-因为你刚刚辞职了 -真是绝配
- Because you've just resigned. - It's a perfect fit.
负责家庭第一法案
Worked on the Families First bill
长得帅 所以死的特别快
and handsome, therefore guilty-looking.
不 不 不
No, no. No.
我知道有人利用了政府数据 故意将广告发给失去亲友的家庭
I know about the targeting of bereaved families
和如何使用联邦数据库
and the use of federal data.
你给我听着  你他妈的狗屎小助理
You listen to me, you little fucking turd's assistant.
你吓唬我不了我
You don't threaten this administration
因为我们他妈的会干掉你
because we will fucking destroy you.
像扒松鼠一样扒了你的皮
We'll skin you like a squirrel,
像清理烟囱一样收拾了你
clean you out like a dirty fucking chimney,
然后用手指像玩弄木偶一样玩弄你
and wear you like a glove puppet with my fingers
挖出你操蛋的死鱼眼
sticking out of your dead fucking eyeballs.
虽然我不支持这种做法
I cannot endorse that message,
但是我还挺赞成的
but I do acknowledge it.
进来
Come inside.
- 嘿 孩子们
- - Hi, boys and girls.
开始讲故事啦 很久很久以前
Now, once upon a time,
有三只小猪
there were three little pigs
和她的母亲---一头老母猪住在一起
with their mom, who was an old sow.
后来她派小猪们去寻找宝藏
And she sent them out to seek their fortune.
好吧 你知道不? 我呢 呃...
Yeah, you know what? I, uh...
想让我辞职 得先给我升职
I think I'm gonna need a bigger title before I agree to resign.
屌丝上尉你看怎么样?
How about Captain Loser?
要不逃兵总局长?
Or Big Chief Skidmark?
总统先生将会以个人名义
And the president will be making another apology
向Jennifer Graham的家人再次致歉
personally to the family of Jennifer Graham.
她只是一个小女孩
She is a young girl who did
从没想过成为国家议论焦点
not ask to become a national debating point.
我应该是他们眼中的出头鸟
I must be their front-runner.
这工作我都干了三年了
I already did the job for three years.
-Amy  -我先挂了
- Amy. - I got to go.
Ben不会被开除 走的人是Dan
Ben's not going. It's Dan.
Mike就要开错人了
Mike's about to saw off the healthy leg.
卧槽!
Oh, fuck!
各位请相信 总统先生会采取必要手段
You can be sure that the president is taking steps
以确保恰当行动的执行
to ensure that appropriate action will be taken.
"小猪猪乖乖 把门开开"
"Little pig, little pig, let me in."
"不开不开我不开
"No, no.
妈妈没回来 谁来也不开"
Not by the hair on my chinny chin chin."
好吧 总统的副助理怎么样?
All right, how about Deputy Assistant to the President?
真有趣
That's funny.
Ben  Mike要宣布开除你
Ben, Mike's about to announce we're firing you.
不 这才有趣
No, that's funny.
大灰狼肚子鼓起来又松下去 把气使劲儿的吹进房子里
So he huffed and he puffed and he blew his house in.
现在有请总统来讲这个故事
Now it's the president's turn to tell the story, please.
- 你是总统吗?  -是的 我是总统
- Child: You're the president? - Yeah, I'm the president.
哇喔
Wow.
Graham一家想要平静的生活
The Graham family have requested privacy
所以我们答应他们，让他们回归正常的生活
and that we allow them to live a normal life.
这是最新讲话  快把它拿给Mike
Here's the new statement. Get that to Mike.
穿高跟鞋我可跑不动
I can't run in these heels.
上帝啊 现在把这个给Mike!
Christian, get that to Mike now!
最终为这件事负责任的人是...
The person with ultimate responsibility is...
是Dan Egan 总统的首席顾问?
is Dan Egan, Chief Counsel to the President?
来这边 小可爱
Come over here, young man.
你好像不太舒服的样子
It looks like you don't feel very good.
-这是你的孩子吗? -他是个小天才
- Is that your son? - He's gifted.
来吧 啊哦
There we go. Uh-oh.
哦
Oh.
-他早餐吃太多了 -好吧
- He did have a big breakfast. - Okay.
你喜欢我读的故事吗?
Do you like the story that I'm reading?
你喜欢?
You do?
哦 你这家伙...
Ew, you guys...
嘿 伙计
Hey, man.
嗯 那啥 慢慢享受你的人生吧
Yeah, well, you know, enjoy it.
我不是来幸灾乐祸的 我也很难过好吗
I'm not here to gloat. I've been through this.
就告诉我那些个狗仔记者在哪些地点蹲守 好吗?
Just tell me which way the vultures are circling, okay?
在西北门有个大型媒体见面会
There's a big media presence by the northwest gate.
要我帮你拿一个吗?
You want me to grab one?
我要从另一个门出去
I'm going out a different door.
今天真他妈是受足了气
Taken enough fucking heat for one day.
你和那些孩子的照片一定会有很好的反响的
That photo of you with the kids will play great.
-哦 真好呀 -是的呢
- Oh, it was so good. - Yeah.
就像是大地母亲与养父母的会面
It was like earth mother meets foster parent
隔壁还有一个给你提词的小女孩
with a hint of girl next door.
-我要一杯苏格兰威士忌 -好的
- I need a scotch. - Yes.
走好 坚强点 伙计
There you go. Stay strong, buddy.
-谢谢 -嘿 我来给你开门吧
- Thanks. - Hey, let me get this for you.
哦 天哪 我本来想说东南门来着
Oh, God, I meant southeast gate.
-Egan先生 你为你的行为感到羞耻吗? -不好意思
- Mr. Egan, do you feel ashamed of your actions? - Excuse me.
我认为...我们当时讨论时
I thought... When we discussed,
我以为Ben是哪个要走的人
I thought that it was Ben who would be going.
哦 对 嗯 实际上 是Bill给了Dan背后一刀
Oh, right. Yeah, actually, Bill suggested Dan.
-啊 -他想了个好点子
- Ah. - He thought it would be a good idea
把Ben留下来
to keep Ben to take the
以防还有什么信息泄露的大篓子
heat in case other data shit hits the fan.
-好主意 对吧? -是的
- Good thought, right? - Yeah.
-尽我的职责罢了 -我 也是
- Just doing my job. - Me, too.
Stevie 我是Dan Egan
Stevie, it's Dan Egan.
那么 呃...我现在又是个待业小青年了
So, um... so it looks like I am a free agent again.
所以 给我回电话吧
Yeah, so give me a call.
这跟上两个短信是一个号码
It's the same number as the last two messages.
嘿 Jen 我是Dan
Hey, Jen, it's Dan.
是你的手机挂了还是我的手机坏了
Either your phone is dead or I am.
明显我希望是第一种情况
So obviously I hope it's the first one.
Josh Stansfield
Josh Stansfield.
你过得怎么样?我是Dan Egan
How are you? It's Dan Egan.
所以 嗯 我...你挂电话了
So, look, I... And you've gone.